KHADIJAH KUYE

Experienced and enthusiastic customer service professional with 3 years experience in customer care, call center and hospitality services. Efficient at handling various calls on dally basis while consistently resolving issues in rapid manners with ability to provide clear customer service in both native(Yoruba) and official(English) languages while building rapport with diverse individuals and handling issues with vast knowledge of customer hospitality and satisfaction.

 \bigcirc

Khadijahkuye99@gmail.com

08103846334, 09012861996.

0

Aduloju Bustop Opp MRS station Ojoo, Ibadan.

曲

18 December, 1994.

EDUCATION

B.Sc. (Hons) Physics with Electronics Osun State University.

2012 - 2016

Osun State

Senior Secondary School Certificate Federal Science and Technical College.

2006-2011

Ogun State

First School Leaving Certificate. **Adsoswac Primary School** 2000 - 2005

Ogun State

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Care and Call Center Agent MTN Nigeria Limited

January 2019 - Present

Achievements/Tasks

Ogun State

- Handling over 50 customer interactions per day, render detailed personal, friendly and polite service to ensure customer retention and satisfaction.
- Timely response to customers' queries and complaint about services, data, connectivity devices, products, malfunctions, promotion and billings.
- Technology savvy with wireless and mobile products.
- Answering and making calls to customers to attend to their requests on product and services, taking memos and maintain files.
- Excellent in listening, written and oral communication skills.
- Research issues on various computer systems and databases to resolve customers' complaints, queries and outline solutions.
- Maintain composure and patience in face of difficult customer situation.
- Document and monitor customer's problems for timely resolution.
- Build and maintain successful relationships with service providers, dealers and consumers.
- Working independently and as a team member in resolving escalated customer issues, request and complaints.

SKILLS

Customer Service, Time management, Multitasking and willing to be trained.

Excellent Telephone, Mail, Text/Chat Etiquettes and Help desk services with Professional phone voice.

Microsoft Office Suite: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, outlook, Office 365.

Strong Listening, Interpersonal and Communication skills, Problem solving, Research, Troubleshooting, Team spirit and Ability to effectively delegate.

Computer proficiency, Hardware and Software maintenance, Familiarity with CRM software, System troubleshooting, Network troubleshooting

WORK EXPERIENCE

Hostel Manager D'setters Consult

June 2018 – December 2018 Achievement/Tasks

Yaba, Lagos State

- Welcomed Registered and assigned rooms to clients.
- Verified customers' credit and established customer's payment mode for accommodation.
- Ensuring and taking records of due entry and exit of customers.
- Promoted the hostel's brand through social media.
- Providing timely solution to occupants complains and requests.
- Maintenance of company's assets and properties.

National Youth Service Corps – NYSC Sheshi Memorial School

May 2017 – April 2018 Achievement/Tasks Katcha, Niger State

<u>LANGUAGES</u>

English Yoruba

CERTIFICATION

Certificate.

Security Specialist.

Jobberman Soft-Skills Training

ICSI | CNSS Certified Network

••••

- Teaching levels of science subject that is appropriate to the maturity of the students and the roles of science in economics and society as a whole.
- Performed various administrative duties such as taking attendance, organizing the classrooms and recording grades.
- Explaining to them the basic concepts of science, Posing problems, questions to students and asking them to provide answers.
- Seek assistance for student who are consistently performing below grade level.
- Maintaining positive relationships with students, parents, community members and staff.

Polio vaccination Independent Monitor / Operator- NYSC World Health Organization (WHO)

December 2017 – April 2018

Achievement/Tasks

Niger State

INTERESTS

Sports (Volleyball, badminton)

Music

Travelling

- Monitored oral polio supplementary immunization activities.
- Taking records of immunized children and households during each exercise.
- Ensuring every household with eligible children is attended to.
- Ensuring accurate household markings.
- Responsible for collecting, entering and submission of data on OPV (oral polio vaccination).
- Providing reports, answers and insights on rounds done in each community.

Technical/ electrical installation and maintenance Team - (INTERN) ZARTECH GROUP OF COMPANES

May 2013 – January Achievement/Tasks

Ibadan, Oyo State

- Assisted in determining requirements and developing plans to ensure smooth installations, maintenance and documentation of new software, hardware and applications.
- Examined installations and observed operations to ensure conformance to equipment specifications.
- Provided timely solution to technical damages and requests.
- Ensured the efficient performance of devices at the plant.

REFEREEE

Available on Request